faceparty.com 2002-10-17

# www.faceparty.com > privacy statement

| **  Privacy Statement**|   
---|---  
  
We will not collect any personal or business information, nor store or share that information with any third party without your express permission. **Why we need Information**  

When you visit our site you will receive explicit advice when we seek to gather information about you. The information you provide is used to produce your web page and any information you supply is displayed to the public on this page, unless otherwise stated.

 **The Registration Process**  

The information harvested during the registration process is used to create your own unique identification as a site visitor/services user and enable us to undertake the various administration processes necessary.

 **Your Unique Identification**  

This identification is provided in the form of a member name and password. It is important that you keep this identification secret to avoid unauthorized use of your account.

 **How we use your Information**  

The information we collect about you or your business enables us to:  
\-    understand your needs  
-    improve our service to you  
-    stay in touch with you through other media as you require  
-    deliver goods and services to the addresses you have provided   
-    enhance and refine existing information we may have acquired from other sources  
-    complete the internal administration necessary to register you and maintain our service to you

 **How do you know if we are gathering Information?**  

Detailed information about you is only collected when you are advised explicitly that is what we are doing and you supply it voluntarily.

 **Sharing Information**  

We may share the information with sub-contractors and partners but only on condition that they comply strictly with our own Supplier Confidentiality Agreement, the Customer Privacy Promise you are currently reading and the EU Directive on Data Protection and the Data Protection Act 1998.

 **Checking Information**  

You can check the accuracy of our records and make modifications at any time in the 'My Account' settings area.

 **Deleting Information**  

You can immediately delete any information we hold about you by using the facilities in My Account. But please remember that deletion of key information may affect your status as a registered user.

 **Sale of Information**  

If you have agreed explicitly to allow us to do so, information about you may be sold or provided to third parties. However, no information will be provided to any other party without your express permission.

 **Legal Disclosure**  

When approached by the appropriate authorities, information about you, your business or account usage may be disclosed but only when legally required under European Law.

 **Security**  

We take all reasonable precautions to protect information about you from loss, misuse and alteration. Agents, partners and sub-contractors who have access to your information have a duty of care as detailed in our contracts with them and are not permitted to use it for any other purpose unless you have given your explicit permission in detail that they may do so.

 **Payment Encryption Technology**  

To protect security we use the most advanced Encryption Technology, anti-intruder and anti-infection techniques when you are providing payment details. You can download an update to the default browser we recommend you use with this site, [Internet Explorer 5](http://www.microsoft.com/ie) or above, which will give you 128 bit encryption.

 **Destruction of Confidential Materials**  

Manual destruction of files, records and computer print-outs containing sensitive data are carried out in a secure way by either internally shredding or using a supplier who uses secure disposal methods.

 **Hackers and Viruses**  

Your registration details are very important - please keep your password and member name secret. It is better for other users to register separately than to share your account access information. We will never write to ask for your login details - be cautious of anyone asking for this information.

 **Automated Collection of Other Information**  

Some non-personal information may be collected automatically, such as the computer operating system and the type of browser software you are using, along with special codes that tell us which pages you have visited. Some information is stored in the form of a 'cookie', a small file which remains on your computer but which acts as a reminder about any preferences you have selected when visiting our sites. We only use 'cookies' to improve our service to you. We may occasionally allow this non-personal data to be used by third party content suppliers, to help us serve you with more relevant content. We may also store your log in details on your computer, but only if you explicitly request us to do so. Remember that if you opt for us to do this, any other user of the same computer can access your account. You can delete this 'cookie' by clicking the Log Out link at the top of any page.

 **Switching Cookies Off**  

Cookies are required in order to become a member of Faceparty, or to use the Faceparty Services.

 **Linked Sites**  

This Privacy Promise does not apply to any third parties over whom we have no control.

 **Changes to our Privacy Promise**  

We reserve the right to change this statement at any time without warning to meet any statutory requirements or changes in the nature of our activities and services. This privacy statement does not form the basis of any contract between any party.

 **Protect your Privacy**  

We caution you against giving out personally identifiable information (such as social security numbers, credit card numbers, names and addresses, driver license numbers, passwords) to strangers online, which may be used for illegal or harmful purposes.

Some personal information you provide to Faceparty may be stored outside of the country in which you reside.
